[Music; pop quiz with dental assisting students]
Hey. Hello.
For your exit question, what is the order for putting on your PPE?
So, you put on your gown first, okay?
[Inaudible]
[Bell]
What does PPE stand for?
PPE means personal protective equipment.
[Bell]
What is the third molar on the lower left?
Seventeen.
[Bell]
What color is the [inaudible] cartridge?
Black.
[Bell]
What color is the needle used for number twenty?
Oh my God!
For your exit question, what surface is the cutting surface of the tooth?
What surface?
Cutting surface.
Cutting?
Yes.
[Bell]
Yay, you're free!
What surface will be touching the tongue?
Lingual.
Oh, good question!
[Bell]
What color will be the needle for number eight?
What number is the lower left second molar?
[Bell]
Yay!
What quadrant is tooth number twenty-seven?
Lower right.
[Music; closing reaction clips]